Dhiraj Salunke

dhirajraje113@gmail.com +91 9923454467 dhiraj.homonovus.in
br/>linkedin.com/in/dhirajsalunke

Summary

Experienced software engineer with 1.5 years of experience developing and enhancing existing and new systems, including both client and server-side development while participating in end-to-end development of software products.

Skills

- · AWS Cloud
- · MEAN stack
- Deep Learning(Tensorflow)

- Python backend development
- Flutter
- Web Development

Experience

HTS Tech Solutions

Software Developer - Pune, Maharashtra

10/2021 - Present

- Lead development of cross-platform app development with flutter and python stack.
- Worked as a full-stack developer with MEAN stack to develop multitier web apps.
- Developed a Face Detection model for online attendance and exam centers with tensorflow.

Flentas technologies PVT. LTD.

Cloud Engineer - Pune, Maharashtra

01/2021 - 09/2021

- Onboarded client's IoT infrastructure on AWS infrastructure.
- Setup analytics, event monitoring, and alerts for IoT devices.
- Developed AWS usage and billing report generator tool.

Binary Dots PVT. LTD.

Flutter intern 08/2020 - 10/2020

- Integrated Firebase google auth in existing app.
- Integrated Ads in existing app.

Education

Computer Engineering

SKN Sinhgad Institute of Technology and Science, Lonavala Pune, Maharashtra

06/2021

- Graduated as Bachelors of Engineering with 7.69 GPA
- Volunteer for developing several web apps for college under the guidance of Google Developer Group and Developer Students Club

Projects

Github URL

Covid counter app

• Flutter app which shows a live count of covid patients in India.

Hello farmer app

• Android app is capable of detecting plant disease from images and making showing some suggestions for a cure.